yooker.com 2019-04-05

# Privacy Policy - Yooker

**Welcome to Yooker.com (the “Site”).**

We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business.  
This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site (“Visitors”) who visit without  
transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by Yooker.com (collectively, “Services”) (“Authorized Customers”).

Yooker.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Yooker.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

**What Personally Identifiable Information is collected**

When visiting Yooker.com , you may provide us with two types of information:

– Personal information you choose to provide. The personal information you choose to provide includes your name and email address when you fill out any of our registration forms.

– Data collected by the log files as you browse the site. Data collected in the log files include your IP, the browser you use, your internet service provider, the pages of our site you visit, and the time you spend in them. We use that information to collect statistical data about our visitors in order to improve our site. None of this recorded information is linked to personally identifiable information.

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

• Personal information you provide may be used occasionally to send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

• Information provided by the log files is collected for statistical purposes and used to help us improve our site.

**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored**

Personally Identifiable Information collected by Yooker.com is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of Yooker.com .

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How Cookies Used on the Site**

Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers.

Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This change may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Links**

This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. You should exercise caution and we encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

Once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.

**What partners or service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorized Customers on the Site**

Yooker.com has entered into and will continue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with a number of vendors.  
Such vendors may have access to certain Personally Identifiable Information on a need to know basis for evaluating Authorized Customers for service eligibility.  
Our privacy policy does not cover their collection or use of this information.  
Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to comply with law. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Authorized Customers.

If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing us on **[Support](https://yooker.com/my-account/private-messages/?username=admin)**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

**How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?**

Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies at **[Support](https://yooker.com/my-account/private-messages/?username=admin)**

**And Finally…**

We thank you for choosing Yooker.com and we look forward to a long a fruitful time together!
